

export const FLASHCARD_DATA = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What are the differences between Functional and Object-Oriented Programming?",
    answer: ["Functional programming relies on mathematical functions, whereas object-oriented programming relies on classes of objects closely associated with functions."],
    hint: [
      'Definitions of both programming methods.', 
      'Key features of both methods.', 
      'Which programming languages they each support.', 
      ''
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:  "Can You Describe the Steps Involved in Software Development?",
    answer: ['1. Planning phase -- developmental gameplan', '2. Coding and development methods', '3. Quality assurance and testing', '4. Completion and deployment'],
    hint: [
      '',
      '',
      '',
      '',
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:  "Tell Me About a Software Development Project You Completed Successfully",
    answer: ['At my last job, where I worked for a software development firm, we developed HR software for a variety of companies. The biggest project I took part in was for a financial institution. The company’s original HR system was outdated and time consuming. We developed a new system where they could handle payroll, time tracking, attendance, training, and hiring in the same place. My primary role was coding, and I mostly worked with C++, Java, and Python'],
    hint: [
      'The type of software development project',
      'Your role in the project',
      'The outcome of the project',
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:  "How do you ensure quality and fix errors?",
    answer: ['Ex.  I usually launch code-based testing to identify and diagnose potential errors. When I helped test the HR software, I asked another member of the team peer review my code. They found one logical error that resulted in incorrect output. Once the coding error was corrected, I used Dynamic Testing to evaluate the software for functionality. By then, it appeared to work as projected'],
    hint: [
      'An example of an error you’ve corrected.',
      'Methods you employ to fix errors',
      'How you identify and diagnose software errors',
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:  "What Programming Languages Are You Proficient In?",
    answer: ['answer '],
    hint: [
      'Programming languages you’re most familiar with',
      'Programming language(s) you’ve used at prior jobs',
      'Examples of previous projects where youve used them',
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:  "Why did you choose a career in software development?",
    answer: ['I’ve always had a knack for solving problems and I feel that software does just that. I chose a career in software development because I find satisfaction in helping consumers, companies, and organizations find the solutions they need. Additionally, I have experience with a variety of programming languages and enjoy working with them. For example...'],
    hint: [
      'Discuss your interests in software development.',
      'Provide an overview of your software development background',
      'Break the ice with your interviewer',
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:  "What kind of tech team dynamic do you excel in?",
    answer: ['Unavailable'],
    hint: [
      'Dont automatically customize your answer for the company. This is your chance to show what matters to you.',
      'Be sure to research the company and how its culture plays out day to day.',
      'Explain how your working style will shape your operations if you were to get the job and accept it.',

    ]
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:  "Lets say there are two kinds of tech workers: the innovators and the executors. Which of these categories do you fit into?",
    answer: ['Why did you choose that answer? What are the benefits vs cons?'],
    hint: [
      'Pause for a few moments and understand what the choices presented mean to you',
      'Explain how the choices will impact the role',
      'Explain how your approach will set you and the company up for success',
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:  "How do you measure success for yourself technically?",
    answer: ['answer '],
    hint: [
      'Dont immediately jump into the metrics. Come up with a mental structure to frame your answer.',
      'Define success by way of a status quo; how you seek to improve it and how you will measure that improvement',
      'Make sure your success criteria have an objective and subjective component to them',
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:  "Why do you think that technical teams need to be inclusive and represent a variety of backgrounds?",
    answer: ['1. Diversity of perspectives', '2. Improved problem-solving', '3. Increased empathy', '4. Broader market reach', '5. Improved employee retention'],
    hint: [
      'Define terms early or ask for clarification',
      'Remember to incorporate the definition into the questions’s premise, which is focused on the team',
      'Explain how inclusivity pays off in the long run',
    ]
  },
]